Jeremy Wuestefeld

Cell: 513-659-5835 | Email: <u>jwuestef@gmail.com</u> | Portfolio: <u>jwuestef.github.io</u> GitHub: https://github.com/jwuestef | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/jeremy-wuestefeld

Junior Web Developer

Experienced problem solver with a background working in fast-paced environments, who enjoys troubleshooting and solving puzzles. Passionate about web development, with a focus on the end-user experience. Collaborative self-motivator who gets excited about new challenges and learning opportunities.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML5 & CSS3
- Responsive UIs
- Angular (4 & JS)
- React-Redux
- Agile Method
- NodeJS
 - deJS MEAN Stack
- RESTful APIs
- MongoDB
- MERN StackPostgreSQL

Experience

Police Officer - Crawfordsville Police Department

05/2014 - 04/2017

- Increased self-initiated field activity by 387% by multitasking and efficiently using worktime.
- Designed and built a custom program that cut time required to run license plates by 75%.
- Active Shooter Instructor trained 33 officers on the appropriate response to active shooter events to decrease civilian casualties.
- Restructured Reserve-Officer Board policies and procedures for the hiring, training, and retention of volunteer reserve officers.
- Fraternal Order Of Police (*Treasurer, Secretary*). Organized inaugural philanthropic 5k fundraiser that increased the Fraternal Order's fundraising by 300% over the previous year.

Security Officer - T & L Enterprises

03/2015 - 12/2016

- Provided a visual deterrent to prevent armed robberies.
- Monitored convenience stores for theft and disruptive customers.
- Reduced shoplifting by \$30,000 / year.

Project Manager - Indiana University

08/2009 - 05/2014

- Designed and built customized tutoring software for all 8 online-employees, which increased
 efficiency by 87.5% for each keyboard shortcut. Designed and built login/logout software for all
 online employees, and software to control 2 multimedia advertising display screens.
- Created and maintained a multi-file Excel spreadsheet to track 60+ employee schedules.
- Monitored and trained team of 4 assistant managers.
- Implemented hiring procedure to filter 80+ applicants for 15 positions.
- Placed all bi-weekly purchasing orders for center.
- Constructed comprehensive student resources for all 9 math classes below Calculus 2.
- Delivered 10 marketing presentations per semester to prospective clients.

Assistant Manager

- Awarded "Supervisor of the Year" in 2012, out of entire School of Science.
- Direct manager for ~10 employees.
- Customer service and daily operations (of a 60+ employee center).

Calculus Tutor

• Tutored students in math, specializing in Calculus 1.

Education

• Javascript Accelerated Learning Program Eleven Fifty Academy, Fishers, Indiana 08/2017

- Police Basic Recruit
 - Indiana Law Enforcement Academy, Plainfield, Indiana
- BS Mechanical Engineering, Minor in Mathematics Purdue University – Indianapolis